# **ASHOT BAGIRAN**

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

+48-505643923 Poznań, Poland https://ashot-bagiran.online

prosperity.devops@gmail.com

SUMMARY

github.com/aoneban LinkedIn: Ashot-Bagiran

I am a web developer with 9 years of experience. But I started my journey in IT almost 10 years ago by creating websites on CMS Joomla and online stores on CMS Opencart. Since about 2020, I have been specializing in front-end applications. My expertise lies in creating web applications using both JavaScript libraries and frameworks as well as vanilla JavaScript. During this time I created dozens of websites. I am also constantly learning and looking for new challenges to apply my knowledge and skills in the field of web development. For example, I am striving to study the full cycle of development including the backend and now I am finishing studying Node.js and have already used it in my latest projects I am sure that by hiring me, any team will gain a wealth of experience and knowledge.

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

JavaScript	React/Redux	Angular/NgRx/RxJS	TypeScript	Webpack/Vite
Node.js	HTML5/CSS3	Git/GitHub	AWS	Figma/PerfectPixel

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

WEB DEVELOPER (2024 - Present)

Freelance

Currently focused on the development of web interfaces and an in-depth study of front-end development, the use of modern technologies and patterns. My aim at the moment is to engage in fullstack development and for this I'm learning Node.js

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

(2021 - 2023)

Oktan

- Work on creating and automating online stores, while simultaneously plunging into a deeper study of frontend development
- Created user interfaces using the React library and Redux for state management.
- Successfully solved performance problems (Memoization, Virtualize Long Lists), as well as structuring components in a reusable.
- Integrated external data sources using REST API.
- I was involved in testing using components such as Jest, React Testing Library и Cypress.

#### FULLSTACK E-COMMERCE DEVELOPER

(2018 - 2021)

Novyj

I was responsible for fully automating online stores on CMS Opencart, including:

- Installation and adaptation of the templates for hosting.
- Automating price list uploads to marketplaces.
- Scraping product photos and descriptions from donor sites.
- Automating pricing based on competitor prices.
- Batch editing of products.
- Integrating payment systems.

### **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION**

REACT COURSE
Rolling Scopes / EPAM

JAVASCRIPT/FRONT-END COURSE
Rolling Scopes / EPAM

( 2021 )

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN ECONOMY AND TRADE MARKETING

(2003)

Belarusian State Economic University, Minsk